

CONTACT

- +306988215196
- Eleftheroupoli Dimadi 19b
- Linkedin

SKILLS

- Programming Languages:
 JavaScript, Python, C, C++,
 C#
- Web Development: HTML, CSS
- Tools: Git, GitHub, npm,
 Microsoft Office, Windows
 OS, Linux, VS Code
- Networking: Network troubleshooting configuration and support
- Soft Skills: Problem-solving, critical thinking, collaboration, adaptability, continuous learning

LANGUAGES

- Greek (Native)
- English (Fluent-C2)
- German (Basic-B1)

KAMPERIS KONSTANTINOS

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | IT SUPPORT SPECIALIST

PROFILE

Highly motivated IT Support Specialist with two years of experience in the tech industry and a solid foundation in Electrical and Computer Engineering. Eager to leverage problem-solving expertise, technical skills, and a passion for continuous learning to transition into a Junior Developer role. Currently honing my programming skills, I am committed to contributing effectively in a collaborative development environment while continually expanding my coding capabilities.

You can track some of my recent activity on my ongoing web portfolio project <u>here</u>.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Support Specialist / ServiceDesk

OCT.2022 - PRESENT

Boss Info AG | Kavala, Greece

- 24/7 Network monitoring using advanced monitoring tools such as OpManager and Paessler PRTG.
- Daily Backup checks and troubleshooting using Veeam software and Kaspersky Suite.
- Threat monitoring, using Avast Business Security, Windows Defender for Business, Barracuda Email Protection, Kaspersky Antivirus for Business.
- Opening and resolving incidents in Navision ERP software.
- Providing NOC services to maintain system up-time and stability.
- Constructing and using scripts for automation purposes using PowerShell and Python.

Exam Invigilator

JUN.2020-APR.2023

TÜV HELLAS | Eastern Macedonia and Thrace, Greece

 Working part-time in examinations prepared by Tuv Hellas, as the company's representative and exam invigilator I developed my communication skills through explaining the digital examination process, troubleshooting any IT problems and maintaining the proper conduct of the examination in a professional manner.

EDUCATION

Master of Engineering - Meng, Electrical and Computer Engineering

2014 - 2022

Democritus University Of Thrace

 Thesis: "Autonomous energy management for EV charging station with PV"